# AARON JOHNSON

## FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



347.786.0266



aaron@ajfs.me



www.ajfs.me



Greater NYC Area

#### **ABOUT ME**

A multi-disciplinary pixel-perefectionist with a love for clean code, I bring a wealth of diverse experience to the table enabling me to hit the ground running on entry. I particularly excel in high-stakes environments where my contributions are essential toward both team and org KPIs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### INTERACTIVE DESIGNER

**POST STUDIOS** 2019 - 2020

- Mockup design for digital interactive ad campaigns using Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator & XD.
- Using HTML, CSS & JavaScript, I craft engaging interactive experiences for both web & mobile.

#### **CREATIVE MANAGER**

**TREMOR VIDEO** 2014 - 2018

- Responsible for the distribution of pre-production mockups & post-production campaigns to various members of the design team; offered design guidance as needed.
- Worked collaboratively with sales and ad ops depts. in educating clientele as to our product offering and platform capabilities.
- Supplied additional support for maximum transparency vsurrounding campaign goals and outcomes.

#### DESIGNER

#### **TREMOR VIDEO** 2013 - 2014

- Designed and built custom advertising experiences using Photoshop, ActionScript & JavaScript.
- Handled all levels of development, from animation to interaction to custom reporting exposure.

#### **RELATED PROFICIENCIES**

HTML NODE

CSS PYTHON

IAVASCRIPT POSTGRES

REACT / REDUX GIT

#### **EDUCATION**

# A.S., DIGITAL MEDIA COMMUNICATIONS KATHARINE GIBBS SCHOOL

2004 - 2006

Web major, focusing on design theory and and application through practical development. Acquired knowledge of Adobe CS, HTML, CSS & ActionScript. Graduated in the top 10 percentile.

### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

#### Lambda School

2019 - 2020

Continuing web development education, focusing on current technologies and best practices. Technologies include React.js for frontend development, Node.js (backend), Python (CS theory, data structures & algorithms) as well as Knex & PostgreSQL for query-building and database management.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **WORLD CORONAVIRUS MAP**

REACT, ARCGIS API, TWITTER API

AJ'S CONWAY GAME OF LIFE

REACT

**GITHUB USER LOOKUP** 

REACT

#### HOBBIES



Coding



Fitness





Reading

Gaming